<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/egyptian-cotton.atom"/>
  <title>American Pillowcase</title>
  <updated>2021-03-01T03:17:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>American Pillowcase</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549141717144</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:17:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:17:00-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-2-pack-striped-standard-size-pillowcases-4-colors-with-wrinkle-guard-to-choose-from-fits-20x26-color-ivory"/>
    <title>100% Egyptian Cotton, 540 Thread Count 2 Pack Striped Standard Size Pillowcases - 4 Colors with Wrinkle Guard to Choose from - fits 20x26 (Color: Ivory)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_ab4fcfd3-d20b-4580-ae0d-6b4c4012bada.jpg?v=1614586621"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            18.51 - 18.60
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-2-pack-striped-standard-size-pillowcases-4-colors-with-wrinkle-guard-to-choose-from-fits-20x26-color-ivory">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">In response to repeated requests from its Amazon customers, American Pillowcase proudly introduces a high-quality, luxuriously soft set of linens that are RELAXATION READY the moment they come out of the dryer. No detail was overlooked in the careful crafting of these 540 thread count striped linens. The 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON fabric is woven using fine yarns, so although it is a high thread count, it is medium weight and perfect for use on warm or cool nights.     100% cotton fibers are ideal for those with sensitive skin as well as comfort and breath-ability. The fabric is expertly finished to ensure its SILKY SOFTNESS, LUSTROUS SHEEN, and WRINKLE RESISTANCE. We have added more stitches to the hems than any other competitor, ensuring the hems never fall apart. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen.<br><br>Package Includes: Two standard pillowcases - 21" x 32" - Fits a standard-sized 20” x 26” pillow<br><br>Luxury Striped Linens<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase silky weave linen set. These items use proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer to make this product perfect for any bed in your home.<br><br>High Thread Count Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our authentic 540 thread count cotton linens are produced using long staple yarns that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 540 are known for a ultra soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Cotton sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. Gently wash with warm water and a standard detergent. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton - Luxuriously-long Staple Cotton Yarns Make These Pillowcases Incredibly Soft and Durable</li>
<li>MEASUREMENTS: STANDARD PILLOWCASES - 21" x 32" - Fits a standard-sized 20” x 26” pillow. Confirm pillow size before ordering. Set of 2 pillowcases included. Bag closure.</li>
<li>A SUMPTUOUS SLEEPING EXPERIENCE THAT WON’T BREAK THE BANK - tested better than all major brands for softness, durability, comfort, wrinkle resistance, and beauty at 50% less than department store prices</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANT - Eco-friendly proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer make this product perfect for any bed in your home</li>
<li>EASY CARE &amp; PRESHRUNK FOR A PERFECT FIT - Machine wash on cold. Tumble dry on low. Do not use bleach or softeners. Preshrunk for a perfectly snug fit on your pillow.</li>
<li>MATCHING DUVET COVER AND SHEETS SOLD SEPARATELY - Purchase a matching duvet cover with your pillowcases for a significant discount! See details below under Special Offers and Product Promotions, or click on the Sold by American Pillowcase link below.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T540 cotton striped</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549141717144</id>
      <title>Ivory - Striped / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.51</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Pillowcases 2 pk Ivory K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>371</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549141717144</id>
      <title>Lt. Blue - Striped / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Pillowcases 2 pk Lt Blue - K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>386</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549140340888</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:16:21-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:16:21-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-egyptian-cotton-hemstitch-dinner-napkins"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase Egyptian Cotton Hemstitch Dinner Napkins - Pick Color</title>
    <s:type>Home</s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_a481b711-90d7-4661-8d74-2a863a4edf9f.jpg?v=1614926622"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Home<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            36.93 - 975.00
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-egyptian-cotton-hemstitch-dinner-napkins">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">These are beautiful, 100% long staple Egyptian cotton napkins.  Perfect for elegant dinner parties or everyday use.  These are sold to hotels and restaurants throughout the world and are made to withstand many washings in a commercial laundry, so they should last a long time in your home. Great for all weddings and dinner parties. In most cases these are more affordable than renting.<br><br>Hemstitch Dinner Napkins   20"x 20"<br><br>Own these superior quality cotton napkins for less than you can rent them. Our elegant napkins are a perfect addition to your dinner service. Choose from Hemstitch or Satin Band knowing you’re getting beautiful, durable, long lasting napkins.<br><br>Beautiful Egyptian Cotton<br><br>The beautiful Egyptian cotton used in these napkins will ensure lasting beauty and quality. These napkins come slightly starched from the factory, this allows them to be cut and sewn perfectly. We recommend they be washed before being used.  They will continually get softer with every wash.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>When its time to wash your napkins simply toss them in your washer on a cold setting with a detergent of your choice.<br><br>Machine dry on medium heat. Remove your napkins when they are 95% dry and iron slightly for a beautiful crisp finish.<br><ul>
<li>100% COTTON – Nearly all napkins selling online are polyester. These will get softer over time</li>
<li>ELEGANT – Beautiful hemstitched, mitered corners, and a linen look will add class to your table</li>
<li>AFFORDABLE – Buying is less expensive than renting just once for an event</li>
<li>PRE-SHUNK - 20"x20". Unlike most napkins, these are pre-shrunk and will remain square</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Napkins</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549140340888</id>
      <title>Ivory / 12</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">36.93</s:price>
      <s:sku>Hemstitch Napkins 12 Ivory</s:sku>
      <s:grams>612</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549140340888</id>
      <title>Off-White / 300</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">975.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>Hemstitch Napkins 300 - White</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139325080</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:40-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:40-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-100-long-staple-cotton-luxury-striped-540-thread-count-flat-sheet-twin-xl-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase 100% Long Staple Cotton Luxury Striped 540 Thread Count Flat Sheet - Pick Size and Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_0f99fb5a-099c-4e44-9301-5b6f5dc67db2.jpg?v=1626238533"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            31.83 - 38.74
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-100-long-staple-cotton-luxury-striped-540-thread-count-flat-sheet-twin-xl-white">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">In response to repeated requests from its Amazon customers, American Pillowcase proudly introduces a high-quality, luxuriously soft set of sheets that is RELAXATION READY the moment it comes out of the dryer. No detail was overlooked in the careful crafting of these 540 thread count striped sheets. The 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON fabric is woven using fine yarns, so although it is a high thread count, it is medium weight and perfect for use on warm or cool nights.     100% cotton fibers are ideal for those with sensitive skin as well as comfort and breath-ability. The fabric is expertly finished to ensure its SILKY SOFTNESS, LUSTROUS SHEEN, and WRINKLE RESISTANCE. We have added more stitches to the hems than any other competitor, ensuring the hems never fall apart. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen.<br><br>Twin XL Set Includes: Flat Sheet -  72" x 102"<br><br>Luxury Striped Sheet Set<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase silky weave sheet set. These sheets use proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer to make this product perfect for any bed in your home.<br><br>High Thread Count Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our authentic 540 thread count cotton sheets are produced using long staple yarns that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 540 are known for a ultra soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Cotton sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. Gently wash with warm water and a standard detergent. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Long Staple Cotton 540 Thread Count – Hypoallergenic, Long Staple Yarns Woven is a Sateen Weave Make These Sheets Incredibly Soft and Luxurious</li>
<li>MEASUREMENTS: FLAT SHEET - 72" x 102" - Fits Twin &amp; Twin XL sized beds, generously sized to ensure easy installation</li>
<li>A SUMPTUOUS SLEEPING EXPERIENCE THAT WON'T BREAK THE BANK - tested better than all major brands for softness, durability, comfort, wrinkle resistance, and beauty at 50% less than department store prices</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANT - Eco-friendly, proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer make this product perfect for any bed in your home</li>
<li>MATCHING SHAMS AND DUVET COVERS SOLD SEPARATELY - Click on the "Sold by American Pillowcase" link below to find matching shams and sheet sets. Purchase matching shams with your duvet cover for a significant discount! See details below</li>
<li>MONEY BACK GUARANTEE - If you don't love your new American Pillowcase fitted sheet return it for a full refund with our 30 day, no-questions-asked guarantee</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bed Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T540 cotton striped</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139325080</id>
      <title>Chocolate / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.51</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Flat Sheet Chocolate Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>753</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139325080</id>
      <title>Gray / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.51</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Flat Sheet Gray Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>753</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139325080</id>
      <title>Ivory / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">38.74</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Flat Sheet Ivory Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1007</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139325080</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.83</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Flat Sheet Lt Blue Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>748</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139259544</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-2-body-pillowcase-set-100-cotton-300-thread-count-21x60-pillow-cover-fits-20-x-54-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase 2 Body Pillowcase Set, 100% Cotton, 300 Thread Count, 21x60 Pillow Cover, Fits 20 x 54, White</title>
    <s:type>Kitchen</s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_0b1e8d14-3fc6-4cfc-843a-26fce3d7ab3c.jpg?v=1614586539"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Kitchen<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            27.95
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">One of the top selling products in the category on Amazon for over 4 years! 100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5 star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. No Zipper to scratch your face or feet. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability. 21 x 60 inches perfectly covers your 20 x 54 pillow with enough overhang to not see the pillow or tuck back into the pillow for a clean look.<br><br>Includes: 2 Body Pillowcases (21"x60" fits 20x54" pillow) with 4” hem<br><br>Body Pillowcase<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase Body Pillowcase. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton<br><br>Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>RICH COLORS / BRIGHT WHITE– Machine wash in cold/medium temperature water and do not use bleach to limit fading.</li>
<li>300 THREAD COUNT - Perfect for maximum comfort and durability. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort.</li>
<li>DETAILS MATTER - 4" Hems add beauty. Oversized pillowcase keeps pillow out of view. Double stitching adds durability. Fine cotton adds breathability and softness. These cannot be sold cheaper without sacrificing on the quality.</li>
<li>100% MONEY BACK GUARANTEE - If not completely satisfied, return with no-questions asked.</li>
<li>MATCHING FLAT AND FITTED SHEETS AND SHAMS – Click on the “Sold by American Pillowcase” link above to find matching sheets and shams as well as entire range of bedding and bath products.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T300 cotton satin weave</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139259544</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">27.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>QI-916W-0C2I</s:sku>
      <s:grams>499</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:32-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-100-egyptian-cotton-luxury-striped-540-thread-count-duvet-cover-with-wrinkle-guard-king-california-king-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase 100% Egyptian Cotton Luxury Striped 540 Thread Count Duvet Cover with Wrinkle Guard - Pick Size and Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_f5943793-f038-4a82-97d8-aa29423f7ef7.jpg?v=1614932135"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            46.51 - 56.65
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-100-egyptian-cotton-luxury-striped-540-thread-count-duvet-cover-with-wrinkle-guard-king-california-king-white">(6 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">In response to repeated requests from its Amazon customers, American Pillowcase proudly introduces a high-quality, luxuriously soft set of linens that are RELAXATION READY the moment they comes out of the dryer. No detail was overlooked in the careful crafting of these 540 thread count striped duvets. The 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON fabric is woven using fine yarns, so although it is a high thread count, it is medium weight and perfect for use on warm or cool nights.     100% cotton fibers are ideal for those with sensitive skin as well as comfort and breath-ability. The fabric is expertly finished to ensure its SILKY SOFTNESS, LUSTROUS SHEEN, and WRINKLE RESISTANCE. We have added more stitches to the hems than any other competitor, ensuring the hems never fall apart. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen.<br><br>Includes:  Duvet Cover - 106" x 94"<br><br>Luxury Striped Linens<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase silky weave Duvet. These Duvet covers use proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer to make this product perfect for any bed in your home.<br><br>High Thread Count Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our authentic 540 thread count cotton linens are produced using long staple yarns that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 540 are known for a ultra soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Cotton sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton linens in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. Gently wash with warm water and a standard detergent. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove linens while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton - Luxuriously-long Staple Cotton Yarns Make This Duvet Cover Incredibly Soft and Durable. Not Polyester Or Microfiber Like Most Duvet Covers.</li>
<li>MEASUREMENTS: DUVET COVER - 106" x 94" - Fits King and Cal King Beds, large opening with hidden button closure for easy insertion of comforter (sold separately)</li>
<li>A SUMPTUOUS SLEEPING EXPERIENCE THAT WON’T BREAK THE BANK - tested better than all major brands for softness, durability, comfort, wrinkle resistance, and beauty at 50% less than department store prices</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANT - Eco-friendly, proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer make this product perfect for any bed in your home</li>
<li>MATCHING SHAMS AND SHEETS SOLD SEPARATELY - Click on the "Sold by American Pillowcase" link below to find matching shams and sheet sets. Purchase matching shams with your duvet cover for a significant discount! See details below.</li>
<li>MATCHING SHAMS AND SHEET SETS - Click on the "Sold by American Pillowcase" to find matching shams and sheet sets by American Pillowcase. Shams are offered at a significant discount if purchased with the duvet cover. See details below</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bed Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T540 cotton striped</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Chocolate / Full-Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">49.22</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - F-Q Chocolate</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1724</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Chocolate / King-California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">56.65</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - K-CalK Chocolate</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2018</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Gray / Full-Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">49.22</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - F-Q Gray</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1842</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Ivory / King-California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">54.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - K-CalK Ivory</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1996</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Light Blue / Full-Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">46.51</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - F-Q Lt Blue</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1701</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549139030168</id>
      <title>Light Blue / King-California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">54.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Duvet - K-CalK Lt Blue</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2018</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138833560</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:23-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:23-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/polycotton-bulk-pack-of-12-king-size-pillowcases-white-200-thread-count-21x40-white-fits-20-x36-pillow-1-dozen-perfect-for-physical-therapy-clinics-hotels-camps"/>
    <title>Polycotton Pillowcases, Bulk Pack, White, 200 Thread Count, Perfect for Physical Therapy Clinics, Hotels, Camps …</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_9cb4269b-0575-4c4c-8061-397d84b275c3.jpg?v=1626238492"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            23.99 - 77.98
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/polycotton-bulk-pack-of-12-king-size-pillowcases-white-200-thread-count-21x40-white-fits-20-x36-pillow-1-dozen-perfect-for-physical-therapy-clinics-hotels-camps">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">These are great for hotels, AirBnB, camps, crafts, physical therapy clinics, embroidery. Please check your pillow size to make sure you order the correct size.
American Pillowcase Body Pillow Cover
100% Percale Cotton
American Pillowcase is bringing you its polycotton two-pack of body pillowcases. This textile is a classic one-over-one-under weave which makes the fabric cool and crisp to touch. This breathable yet medium weight material keeps you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count does not mean better quality or comfort, but this 200 count is perfect for maximum durability and comfort. Hotel quality, made of 60% cotton 40% polyester for cotton-rich comfort.
Durable quality
Luxurious
200 Thread Count Percale Poly Cotton
Durable quality
Luxurious
200 Thread Count Percale Poly Cotton
200 Thread Count Percale Poly Cotton
Our percale weave cotton pillowcases are produced using a one over one under pattern, creating a tight weave that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability. These are great if you want less wrinkling than cotton. It you want to print or tie dye them, 100% cotton works better, but these work as well.</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T220 cotton</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138833560</id>
      <title>White / Body - Qty 2</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">23.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Poly Cotton T200 2 pack - Body - White</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1379</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138833560</id>
      <title>White / King - 24 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">77.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>Poly Cotton T200 24 pack - K - White</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1379</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138833560</id>
      <title>White / Standard - 12 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>PolyCottonT20012pack-S-W</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1379</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138833560</id>
      <title>white / King - 12 Pack</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">36.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Poly Cotton T200 12 pack - K - White</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1379</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:20-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:20-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/20-queen-size-100-cotton-white-t220-percale-wholesale-bulk-pillowcases-for-tie-dying-silk-screening-hotels-crafts-camps-parties-physical-therapy"/>
    <title>100% Cotton White T220 Percale Wholesale Bulk Pillowcases for Tie-Dying, Silk Screening, Hotels, Crafts, Camps, Parties, Physical Therapy - Pick Size</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_c0782fc5-defd-4077-a25c-43e7324c98ef.jpg?v=1614586595"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            11.68 - 365.65
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/20-queen-size-100-cotton-white-t220-percale-wholesale-bulk-pillowcases-for-tie-dying-silk-screening-hotels-crafts-camps-parties-physical-therapy">(6 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">American Pillowcase is bringing you its 100% luxury Egyptian Cotton made from long staple yarns. This Percale textile is a classic one-over-one-under weave which makes the fabric cool and crisp to touch. This breathable yet medium weight material keeps you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count does not mean better quality or comfort, but this 220 count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. Even for those with sensitive skin. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen. The hems will help prevent falling apart as extra stitches have been added to ensure a long-lasting product.
Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with these American Pillowcase pillowcases. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, crisp Percale weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.
220 Thread Count Percale Egyption Cotton
Our percale weave cotton pillowcases are produced using a one over one under pattern, creating a tight weave that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.
Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a crisp, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Percale linens resist pilling. These linens will develop a softer feel with every washing.
Care Instructions
You should always wash your cotton percale pillowcases in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A gentle wash cycle with a cold temperature setting, and a mild detergent is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.
Removing cotton pillowcases promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove pillowcases while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton pillowcases. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T220 cotton</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / King - Qty 2</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">13.29</s:price>
      <s:sku>T220 pillowcase king - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>181</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / King - Qty 20</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">72.45</s:price>
      <s:sku>T220 pillowcase king - 20</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2672</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / Queen - Qty 20</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">69.06</s:price>
      <s:sku>T220 pillowcase queen- 20</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2404</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / Standard - Qty 120</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">365.65</s:price>
      <s:sku>T220 pillowcase standard - 120</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / Standard - Qty 2</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">11.68</s:price>
      <s:sku>T220 pillowcase standard-  2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138702488</id>
      <title>White - Cotton / Standard - Qty 20</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">96.30</s:price>
      <s:sku>FO-1PO0-248L</s:sku>
      <s:grams>2064</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:16-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:16-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/luxury-egyptian-cotton-300-thread-count-body-pillowcase-fits-20-x-54-inch-body-pillow-envelope-closure-qty-1-pink"/>
    <title>Luxury Egyptian Cotton 300 Thread Count Body Pillowcase - fits 20 x 54 Inch Body Pillow, Envelope Closure - Pick Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_7d5131b1-8051-485b-94ea-c2f26319afc7.jpg?v=1626238507"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            12.95 - 17.45
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/luxury-egyptian-cotton-300-thread-count-body-pillowcase-fits-20-x-54-inch-body-pillow-envelope-closure-qty-1-pink">(5 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">One of the top selling products in the category on Amazon for over 4 years! 100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5 star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. No Zipper to scratch your face or feet. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability. 21 x 60 inches perfectly covers your 20 x 54 pillow. Envelope closure for a clean, finish and No uncomfortable zipper!<br><br>Includes: One Body Pillowcase (21"x60" fits 20x54" pillow)<br><br>Body Pillowcase<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase Body Pillowcase. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton<br><br>Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton 300 Thread Count - Luxuriously-long Staple Cotton Yarns Woven in a Sateen Weave Make These Sheets Incredibly Soft and Durable</li>
<li>ENVELOPE CLOSURE - Clean, Finish Look and No uncomfortable zipper!</li>
<li>300 THREAD COUNT - Perfect for maximum comfort and durability. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort.</li>
<li>DETAILS MATTER – Double stitching adds durability. Fine cotton adds breathability and softness. These cannot be sold cheaper without sacrificing on the quality</li>
<li>100% MONEY BACK GUARANTEE – If not completely satisfied, return with no-questions asked.</li>
<li>MATCHING SHEETS, SHAMS, AND PILLOWCASES – Click on the “Sold by American Pillowcase” link above to find matching fitted and flat sheets and all other sizes of shams and pillowcases</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T300 cotton satin weave</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
      <title>Black / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">17.45</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 Body Pillowcase Black Env-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>204</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
      <title>Ivory / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.58</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 Body Pillowcase Ivory Env-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>181</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">17.45</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 Body Pillowcase Lt Blue Env-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>198</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
      <title>Pink / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.58</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 Body Pillowcase Pink Env-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>181</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138636952</id>
      <title>White / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.95</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 Body Pillowcase White Env-1</s:sku>
      <s:grams>227</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-genuine-egyptian-cotton-300-thread-count-body-pillow-cover-21-x-60-inch-light-blue"/>
    <title>100% Genuine Egyptian Cotton 300 Thread Count Body Pillow Cover, 21 x 60 Inch - Pick Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_1d8585d9-56b9-4d4c-9916-d9efaba2f32d.jpg?v=1621014866"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            18.50 - 20.00
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-genuine-egyptian-cotton-300-thread-count-body-pillow-cover-21-x-60-inch-light-blue">(6 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">One of the top selling products in the category on the Web for over 4 years! 100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5-star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. No Zipper to scratch your face or feet. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability. 21 x 60 inches perfectly covers your 20 x 54 pillow with enough overhang to not see the pillow or tuck back into the pillow for a clean look.<br><br>Includes: One Body Pillowcase (21"x60" fits 20x54" pillow) with 4” hem<br><br>Body Pillowcase<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase Body Pillowcase. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton<br><br>Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><br><br>100% Egyptian Cotton – Hypoallergenic, Super Long Staple Yarns Woven is a Sateen Weave Making These Pillowcases Incredibly Soft and Luxurious.<br>Body Pillow Pillowcase 21" X 60" with 4" hem (fits 20" x 54")<br>540 Thread Count with Wrinkle Guard.<br>Same fabric that is used in American Pillowcase's sheet sets<br>Amazingly soft fabric<br>Now also selling discounted Standard, Queen, and King Pillowcases.</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T300 cotton satin weave</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Black / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Black</s:sku>
      <s:grams>235</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Gray / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Gray</s:sku>
      <s:grams>258</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Ivory / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Ivory-i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>142</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Lt Blue</s:sku>
      <s:grams>286</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Pink / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">20.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Pink-i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>159</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138440344</id>
      <title>Sage / Body 21x60, 20x54, 20 x 54</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>Pillowcase-Body-Sage-i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>159</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138342040</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:07-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:07-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/body-pillowcase-100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-21-x-60-pillow-cover-striped-with-wrinkle-guard-by-fits-20-x-54-light-blue"/>
    <title>Body Pillowcase, 100% Egyptian Cotton, 540 Thread Count, 21&quot; x 60&quot; Pillow Cover, Striped with Wrinkle Guard by Fits 20&quot; x 54&quot;, Pick Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_4967c54b-a9c5-4b57-b97c-f2148f2b3623.jpg?v=1614586507"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.43 - 19.98
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/body-pillowcase-100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-21-x-60-pillow-cover-striped-with-wrinkle-guard-by-fits-20-x-54-light-blue">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">In response to repeated requests from its Amazon customers, American Pillowcase proudly introduces a high-quality, luxuriously soft set of linens that are RELAXATION READY the moment they come out of the dryer. No detail was overlooked in the careful crafting of these 540 thread count striped linens. The 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON fabric is woven using fine yarns, so although it is a high thread count, it is medium weight and perfect for use on warm or cool nights.     100% cotton fibers are ideal for those with sensitive skin as well as comfort and breath-ability. The fabric is expertly finished to ensure its SILKY SOFTNESS, LUSTROUS SHEEN, and WRINKLE RESISTANCE. We have added more stitches to the hems than any other competitor, ensuring the hems never fall apart. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen.<br><br>Package Includes:  21” x 60” Body Pillowcase extends 6” past your 54” body pillow<br><br>Luxury Striped Linens<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase silky weave linen set. These items use proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer to make this product perfect for any bed in your home.<br><br>High Thread Count Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our authentic 540 thread count cotton linens are produced using long staple yarns that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 540 are known for a ultra soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Cotton sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. Gently wash with warm water and a standard detergent. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton - Luxuriously-long Staple Cotton Yarns Make These Pillowcases Incredibly Soft and Durable</li>
<li>OVERSIZED BAG STYLE – 21”x60” extends 6” past your 54” body pillow. You can leave open or tuck excess back into pillow for a beautiful clean look. No uncomfortable zipper!</li>
<li>A SUMPTUOUS SLEEPING EXPERIENCE THAT WON’T BREAK THE BANK - tested better than all major brands for softness, durability, comfort, wrinkle resistance, and beauty at 50% less than department store prices</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANT - Eco-friendly proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer make this product perfect for any bed in your home</li>
<li>EASY CARE &amp; PRESHRUNK FOR A PERFECT FIT - Machine wash on cold. Tumble dry on low. Do not use bleach or softeners. Preshrunk for a perfectly snug fit on your pillow.</li>
<li>MATCHING DUVET COVER AND SHEETS SOLD SEPARATELY - Purchase matching duvet cover with your pillowcase for a significant discount! See details below under Special Offers and Product Promotions, or click on the Sold by American Pillowcase link below.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T540 cotton striped</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138342040</id>
      <title>Chocolate / 21x60 - Fits 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.43</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Pillowcase 1 Chocolate - B</s:sku>
      <s:grams>181</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138342040</id>
      <title>White / 21x60 - Fits 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Stripe Pillowcases 1 pc White B</s:sku>
      <s:grams>289</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:15:06-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:15:06-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-fitted-bed-sheet-100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-twin-xl-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase Fitted Bed Sheet, 100% Egyptian Cotton, 540 Thread Count (Pick Size and Color)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_71a6b96e-8d59-4c37-88f3-095b05c3e257.jpg?v=1626238457"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            31.66 - 39.60
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-fitted-bed-sheet-100-egyptian-cotton-540-thread-count-twin-xl-white">(11 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">In response to repeated requests from its Amazon customers, American Pillowcase proudly introduces a high-quality, luxuriously soft set of sheets that is RELAXATION READY the moment it comes out of the dryer. No detail was overlooked in the careful crafting of these 540 thread count striped sheets. The 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON fabric is woven using fine yarns, so although it is a high thread count, it is medium weight and perfect for use on warm or cool nights.     100% cotton fibers are ideal for those with sensitive skin as well as comfort and breath-ability. The fabric is expertly finished to ensure its SILKY SOFTNESS, LUSTROUS SHEEN, and WRINKLE RESISTANCE. We have added more stitches to the hems than any other competitor, ensuring the hems never fall apart. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen.<br><br>California King Includes: One Deep Pocket Fitted Sheet (72" x 84" fits mattresses up to 18") with all-around elastic<br><br>Luxury Striped Sheet Set<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase silky weave sheet set. These sheets use proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer to make this product perfect for any bed in your home.<br><br>High Thread Count Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our authentic 540 thread count cotton sheets are produced using long staple yarns that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 540 are known for a ultra soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Cotton sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. Gently wash with warm water and a standard detergent. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton 540 Thread Count – Hypoallergenic, Long Staple Yarns Woven is a Sateen Weave Make These Sheets Incredibly Soft and Luxurious</li>
<li>MEASUREMENTS: FITTED SHEET - 72" x 84" - Fits California King size bed, deep pockets to ensure easily installation without the worry of them slipping up</li>
<li>A SUMPTUOUS SLEEPING EXPERIENCE THAT WON'T BREAK THE BANK - tested better than all major brands for softness, durability, comfort, wrinkle resistance, and beauty at 50% less than department store prices</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANT - Eco-friendly, proprietary processing to limit wrinkling out of the dryer make this product perfect for any bed in your home</li>
<li>MATCHING SHAMS AND DUVET COVERS SOLD SEPARATELY - Click on the "Sold by American Pillowcase" link below to find matching shams and sheet sets. Purchase matching shams with your duvet cover for a significant discount! See details below</li>
<li>MONEY BACK GUARANTEE - If you don't love your new American Pillowcase fitted sheet return it for a full refund with our 30 day, no-questions-asked guarantee</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bed Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T540 cotton striped</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>White / California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">38.74</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet White Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1111</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>White / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">38.72</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet White Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>939</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>White / Twin</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.43</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet White Twin</s:sku>
      <s:grams>531</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>White / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.66</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet White Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>658</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Chocolate / California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Chocolate Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1089</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Chocolate / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.97</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Chocolate Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>699</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Gray / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Gray Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>885</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Gray / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">39.60</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Gray Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>640</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Ivory / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.58</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Ivory Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>880</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / California King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">38.74</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Lt Blue Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>998</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549138309272</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">32.43</s:price>
      <s:sku>T540 Fitted Sheet Lt Blue Twin XL-FBM</s:sku>
      <s:grams>640</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:14:56-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:14:56-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-euro-shams-26x26-set-of-2-pillow-covers-luxury-100-egyptian-cotton-2-pack-european-26-x-26-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase Shams, Luxury 100% Egyptian Cotton - Pick Size and Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_1143aeb1-8245-42b6-86f8-0ac724807c38.jpg?v=1614926809"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            14.97 - 25.99
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-euro-shams-26x26-set-of-2-pillow-covers-luxury-100-egyptian-cotton-2-pack-european-26-x-26-white">(14 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">I really like the look of shams on my pillows much more than pillowcases, but it is very difficult to find high quality, luxury cotton shams without paying a fortune. For years, I made these shams for some of the finest hotels in the world and guests would call to ask if I would sell them. Now I do!<br><br>100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5 star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability.<br><br>Includes: 2 Standard Shams 21" x 26"<br><br>Standard Sham<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with these American Pillowcase Pillow Shams. These shams are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton<br><br>Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton - Luxuriously-long Staple Cotton Yarns Make These Pillow Shams Incredibly Soft and Durable</li>
<li>STANDARD PILLOW SHAMS – Perfectly fits a 20” x 26” pillow. Confirm pillow size before ordering. Quantity 2</li>
<li>LUXURY 100% EGYPTIAN COTTON - Shams with 2” flange on all four sides and overlapping fabric in back for finished look</li>
<li>HIGHEST QUALITY CONSTRUCTION - Made of 100% combed cotton spun into compact yarns and woven into a 300 thread count fabric. Very rare to use such beautiful yarns for retail sheeting</li>
<li>BIO-POLISHED - You’ll feel the fantastic softness at first touch. Sateen weave and MERCERIZED for a beautiful sheen.</li>
<li>EASY CARE &amp; PRESHRUNK FOR A PERFECT FIT - Machine wash on cold. Tumble dry on low. Do not use bleach or softeners. Preshrunk for a perfecly snug fit on your pillow, please confirm your pillow size before placing your order.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Black - Solid 300 Thread Count / 26x26 Euro</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.97</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300--Black Euro</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Black - Solid 300 Thread Count / Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.97</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300--Black S</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Ivory - Solid 300 Thread Count / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Ivory K -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Ivory - Striped 540 Thread Count / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams - T540-Ivory K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Ivory - Striped 540 Thread Count / Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.04</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams - T540-Ivory S</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>Light Blue - Striped 540 Thread Count / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">21.84</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams - T540-Lt Blue K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / 18x18 Square</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">18.04</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Euro-18x18-2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / 26x26 Euro</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.04</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Euro-2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / Boudoir</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">20.31</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Boudoir-2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-King Size</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">20.89</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Solid 300 Thread Count / Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">20.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams-T300-Standard</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Striped 540 Thread Count / Boudoir</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams - T540-White Boudoir</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137981592</id>
      <title>White - Striped 540 Thread Count / King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>Shams - T540-White K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>454</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:14:52-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:14:52-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-king-cal-king-size-flat-sheet-only-300-thread-count-100-long-staple-cotton-pieces-sold-separately-for-set-guarantee-ivory"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase Flat Sheet, 300 Thread Count 100% Long Staple Cotton - Pick Size and Color</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_9a2e64d0-2468-4951-9514-490222156784.jpg?v=1628963179"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            20.75 - 37.34
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-king-cal-king-size-flat-sheet-only-300-thread-count-100-long-staple-cotton-pieces-sold-separately-for-set-guarantee-ivory">(26 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">It has been hard in the past to find high quality sheets without having to buy the entire set.... until now! Choose your different colors and/or  different size fitted sheets, flat sheets, and pillowcase pairs  separately without sacrificing any quality. Be creative and use different color sheets for the bottom, top, and pillowcases. Find complimentary flat sheets and pillowcases by clicking on the American Pillowcase store name above.
100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5 star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability.
Includes: 1 King/Cali King Flat sheet 110" x 106" with  4" hem
King/Cali King Flat Sheet
Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with these American Pillowcase Sheets. These sheets are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.
300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton
Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.
Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.
Care Instructions
You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bed Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T300 cotton satin weave</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Black / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.66</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Black Full</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Black / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Black K Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Black / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.54</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Black Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Gray / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.91</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Gray Full</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Gray / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Gray K Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Gray / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">27.31</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Gray Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Gray / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">23.86</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Gray Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Ivory / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">28.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Ivory Full -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Ivory / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">37.34</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Ivory K Cal King -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Ivory / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">28.75</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Ivory Queen -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Ivory / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Ivory Twin XL -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.66</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Lt Blue Full</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.68</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Lt Blue K Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">27.31</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Lt Blue Queen</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">23.86</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Lt Blue Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Pink / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.45</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Pink Full -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Pink / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">33.34</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Pink K Cal King -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Pink / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.14</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Pink Queen -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Pink / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Pink Twin XL -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Sage / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.66</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Green Full -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Sage / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">31.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Green K Cal King -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Sage / Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">28.75</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Green Queen -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>Sage / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">23.86</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet Green Twin XL -i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>White / Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">23.49</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet White Full</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>White / King / Cal King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">33.03</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet White K Cal King</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137883288</id>
      <title>White / Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">20.75</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 1 Flat Sheet White Twin XL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>907</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:14:47-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:14:47-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-flat-sheet-100-percale-egyptian-cotton-400-thread-count-queen-white"/>
    <title>American Pillowcase Sheets &amp; Pillowcases, 100% Percale Egyptian Cotton, 400 Thread Count, Pick One</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_1ac00af1-ced8-4c4f-8c6f-6700cbb1bc77.jpg?v=1626238471"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            16.98 - 28.72
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-flat-sheet-100-percale-egyptian-cotton-400-thread-count-queen-white">(7 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">American Pillowcase is bringing you their 100% luxury Egyptian Cotton  made from long staple yarns. This Percale textile is a classic one-over-one-under weave which makes the fabric cool and crisp to touch.  This breathable yet medium weight material keeps you cool in the summer  and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count does not mean better  quality or comfort, but this 400 count is perfect for maximum comfort  and durability. Even for those with sensitive skin. The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen. The hems will help prevent falling apart as extra stitches have been added  to ensure a long-lasting product.<br><br>Includes:1 -  110" x 106" White Flat Sheet<br><br>Flat Sheet<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with this American Pillowcase Flat Sheet. This flat sheet is made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, crisp Percale weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>400 Thread Count Percale Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our percale weave cotton sheets are produced using a one over one under pattern, creating a tight weave that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a crisp, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Percale sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton percale sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A gentle wash cycle with a cold temperature setting, and a mild detergent is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br><br>Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Combed Egyptian Cotton – Hypoallergenic, Luxurious, Soft, Durable</li>
<li>KING/CALIFORNIA KING FLAT SHEET - Measuring 110" x 106" and a 4" hem, this flat sheet is generous in size and will provide a smooth transition into a deep sleep. This breathable yet medium weight material keeps you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter.</li>
<li>HIGH-QUALITY CONSTRUCTION - These crisp sheets are made of luxurious 100% Egyptian cotton, beautifully woven in a way to give these sheets a classic, clean look. Double stitching ensures durability for this 400 thread count linen.</li>
<li>LIMITED WRINKLES - The classic percale weave is a unique one-over-one-under that makes this fabric cool and crisp to the touch, with a desirable textured look. While it is cotton, some wrinkles may occur but due to the structure this is limited.</li>
<li>HYPOALLERGENIC - The hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a sateen finish for a smooth, satin-like surface and luminous sheen.</li>
<li>MONEY BACK GUARANTEE – American Pillowcase stands behind their products and offers a hassle free, no questions asked return process.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bed Sheets</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T400 cotton percale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Fitted Sheet - Twin</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">25.67</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Fitted Sheet White - T</s:sku>
      <s:grams>544</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Flat Sheet - Full</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">28.72</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Flat Sheet White - F</s:sku>
      <s:grams>816</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Flat Sheet - Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">27.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Flat Sheet White - Q</s:sku>
      <s:grams>998</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Flat Sheet - Twin / Twin XL</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">24.89</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Flat Sheet White - T-TXL</s:sku>
      <s:grams>662</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Pillowcases - King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">17.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Pillowcase 2x White - K</s:sku>
      <s:grams>357</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Pillowcases - Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Pillowcase 2x White - Q</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137719448</id>
      <title>Pillowcases - Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Pillowcase 2x White - S</s:sku>
      <s:grams>266</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:14:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:14:32-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-white-standard-pillow-cases-set-of-2-100-cotton-pillow-cases-300t-hypoallergenic-soft-pillow-cases-standard-size"/>
    <title>100% Cotton Pillow Cases, 300 Thread Count, Hypoallergenic, Soft. Pick Size and Color</title>
    <s:type>Kitchen</s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_5a7028b0-5f0c-4b5b-b6eb-0c471831beae.jpg?v=1626238463"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Kitchen<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            12.34 - 16.98
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/american-pillowcase-white-standard-pillow-cases-set-of-2-100-cotton-pillow-cases-300t-hypoallergenic-soft-pillow-cases-standard-size">(20 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">100% Long Staple Cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 Thread Count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5 star, luxury hotels for years. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. Hypoallergenic, will reduce allergens. Sateen Finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double Stitched Seams for quality and durability.<br><br>Includes: 2 Standard Pillowcases 21" x 30" with 4” hem<br><br>Standard Pillowcase<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with these American Pillowcase Pillowcases. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, soft sateen weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>300 Thread Count Egyptian Cotton<br><br>Our 300 thread count Egyptian cotton is made with a sateen four over one weave allowing for a silky soft feel. These pillowcases feel smooth and fresh providing the comfort you need for quality nights rest.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a soft, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton sheets in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A normal wash cycle with a warm temperature setting is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens. Removing cotton sheets promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove sheets while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton sheets...<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton – Hypoallergenic, Long Staple Yarns Woven in a Sateen Weave Make These Pillowcases Incredibly Soft and Luxurious.</li>
<li>Imported</li>
<li>RICH COLORS / BRIGHT WHITE– Machine wash in cold/medium temperature water and do not use bleach to limit fading.</li>
<li>300 THREAD COUNT - Perfect for maximum comfort and durability. Higher thread count does not mean better quality or comfort. Measure: 21 inch x 32 inches, fits 20" x 26" Pillows</li>
<li>DETAILS MATTER - 4" Hems add beauty. Oversized pillowcase keeps pillow out of view. Double stitching adds durability. Fine cotton adds breathability and softness. These cannot be sold cheaper without sacrificing on the quality.</li>
<li>100% MONEY BACK GUARANTEE - If not completely satisfied, return with no-questions asked.</li>
<li>MATCHING FLAT AND FITTED SHEETS AND SHAMS – Click on the “Sold by American Pillowcase” link above to find matching sheets and shams as well as entire range of bedding and bath products. If it does not say "Sold by American Pillowcase", the pillowcases you get will be poor quality knock-offs. Do not buy these.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T300 cotton satin weave</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>White / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase standard - 2c</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>White / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">13.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase queen - 2-i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>White / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.14</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase king - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>363</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Black / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase BLACK standard - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Black / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase BLACK queen - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>295</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Black / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase BLACK king - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>363</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Gray / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.24</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase GRAY queen - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Gray / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.14</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase GRAY king - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Ivory / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.34</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase IVORY standard - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Ivory / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase IVORY queen - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Ivory / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase IVORY king - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase Lt Blue standard - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>249</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase Lt Blue queen - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>295</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Lt Blue / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase Lt Blue king - 2</s:sku>
      <s:grams>340</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Pink / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase PINK standard - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>227</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Pink / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase PINK queen - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>295</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Pink / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.98</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase PINK king - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>363</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Sage / 21x30 Standard</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">12.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase SAGE standard - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>272</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Sage / 21x36 Queen</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.99</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase SAGE queen - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>318</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137326232</id>
      <title>Sage / 21x42 King</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.14</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase SAGE king - 2i</s:sku>
      <s:grams>363</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:14:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:14:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-genuine-luxury-egyptian-cotton-400-thread-count-percale-body-pillowcase-fits-20-x-54-inch-body-pillow-envelope-closure-qty-1-white"/>
    <title>Genuine Luxury Egyptian Cotton 400 Thread Count Percale Body Pillowcase fits 20 x 54 Inch Body Pillow, Envelope Closure (Qty. 1 Choose Color)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_abdc6f7b-81a4-4a83-ba51-52e4e1d1df7a.jpg?v=1614586473"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            11.78 - 22.31
            <a href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/100-genuine-luxury-egyptian-cotton-400-thread-count-percale-body-pillowcase-fits-20-x-54-inch-body-pillow-envelope-closure-qty-1-white">(6 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">American Pillowcase is bringing you their 100% luxury Egyptian Cotton  made from long staple yarns. This Percale textile is a classic one-over-one-under weave which makes the fabric cool and crisp to touch.  This breathable yet medium weight material keeps you cool in the summer  and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count does not mean better  quality or comfort, but this 400 count is perfect for maximum comfort  and durability. Even for those with sensitive skin. The  hypoallergenic qualities will reduce allergens but still showcases a smooth finish for a satin-like surface and luminous sheen. The hems will help prevent falling apart as extra stitches have been added  to ensure a long-lasting product.   21 x 60 inches perfectly covers your 20 x 54 pillow with enough  overhang to not see the pillow or tuck back into the pillow for a clean  look.<br><br>Includes: 1 -  21" x 60" Body Pillowcase<br><br>Body Pillow Case<br><br>Add some luxurious comfort to your bedroom with these American Pillowcase Body Pillowcases. These pillowcases are made of 100% Egyptian cotton with a breathable, crisp Percale weave comparable to those found in 5 star hotels around the globe.<br><br>400 Thread Count Percale Egyption Cotton<br><br>Our percale weave cotton pillowcases are produced using a one over one under pattern, creating a tight weave that pairs long lasting beauty with exceptional strength and durability.<br><br>Thread count references the number of threads per square inch of fabric. Cotton linens with a thread count of 200-400 are known for a crisp, clean feel that is breathable and wicks away moisture. Percale sheets resist pilling, especially in thread counts of 400 or more. These sheets will develop a softer feel with every washing.<br><br>Care Instructions<br><br>You should always wash your cotton percale pillowcases in a separate load than your normal laundry, as zippers, hooks and buttons could possibly damage cotton linens. A gentle wash cycle with a cold temperature setting, and a mild detergent is recommended. Quality, pH balanced detergents are best when washing fine cotton linens. Do not use chlorinated bleach as it can damage quality cotton bedding fibers. If needed, non-chlorinated bleach can be used with white and ivory cotton linens.<br><br>Removing cotton pillowcases promptly after washing will help reduce wrinkling. Shaking linens out before placing them in the dryer will reduce wrinkling also. When drying, use a warm setting, remove pillowcases while they are still slightly damp and hang to finish drying. Ironing is optional but not usually necessary for cotton pillowcases. However, some people prefer to iron them for a crisper appearance.<br><ul>
<li>100% Egyptian Cotton – Hypoallergenic, Long Staple Yarns Woven in a Percale Weave Make These Pillowcases Delightfully Crisp to the Touch.</li>
<li>1 WHITE BODY PILLOWCASE - 21x60, 4" Hem (fits 20"x54" Body Pillow Perfectly)</li>
<li>400 THREAD COUNT - Single yarns for amazing durability. Perfect weight. Beautifully woven. Double stitching.</li>
<li>PERCALE WEAVE - classic, hard to find one-over-one-under weave makes this fabric cool and crisp to touch with textured look</li>
<li>100% MONEY BACK GUARANTEE - If not completely satisfied, return with no-questions asked</li>
<li>EASY CARE - Machine wash warm, no bleach, no fabric softener, tumble dry low.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Bedroom</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Egyptian Cotton</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases</s:tag>
    <s:tag>T400 cotton percale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>White - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 White</s:sku>
      <s:grams>227</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>Black - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.34</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 Black</s:sku>
      <s:grams>249</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>Gray - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">15.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 Gray</s:sku>
      <s:grams>181</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>Ivory - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">11.78</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 Ivory</s:sku>
      <s:grams>230</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>Lt Blue - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">15.36</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 Lt Blue</s:sku>
      <s:grams>45</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549137293464</id>
      <title>Sage - Envelope Closure / 20x54 Body Pillowcase</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">22.31</s:price>
      <s:sku>T400 Percale Body PC Env-1 Sage</s:sku>
      <s:grams>232</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
