<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/collections/pillowcase-wholesale.atom"/>
  <title>American Pillowcase</title>
  <updated>2021-03-05T03:13:43-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>American Pillowcase</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6557723361432</id>
    <published>2021-03-05T03:13:43-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-05T03:13:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/wholesale-box-of-140-standard-size-microfiber-pillowcases"/>
    <title>Wholesale Box of 140 Standard Size Microfiber Pillowcases</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_98e3313f-a710-43f4-a38c-e2f0bf80270d.jpg?v=1614932023"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            400.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Add some comfort to your bedroom with American Pillowcase microfiber pillowcases. These pillowcases are made of 100% Microfiber for comfort and durability. The fabric is brushed giving it that peach-fuzz feel that makes microfiber so smooth and silky.<br><br>With stain, fade, and wrinkle resistant material, the pillowcases will maintain their high quality for years to come. You can give your bedroom a cohesive, stylish look with the matching pillowcases with 2-inch hems. When it is time to wash your pre-shrunk pillowcases, simply toss them into the washing machine, wash with cool water, and dry.<br><br><br>100% Brushed Microfiber - Super Soft, Stain- and Wrinkle-Resistant<br><br><br>Designed with 100% Brushed Microfiber, a stain, wrinkle, and fade resistant choice for your convenience<br><br><br>Breathable fabric is lightweight and soft so you can stay cool in the summer and warm in the winter<br><br><br>2-inch hems for a polished bedroom look<br><br><br>Easy Care Instructions: Wash separately in warm water. Do not bleach or use fabric softener. Quick Drying</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6557723361432</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">400.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>Microfiber-Pillowcase-Wholesale-Box</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549150957720</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:24:16-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:24:16-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/wholesale-box-of-120-pillowcases-standard-size-4-hems-300-thread-count-100-long-staple-egyptian-cotton"/>
    <title>Wholesale box of 120 Pillowcases. Standard Size 4&quot; Hems, 300 Thread Count 100% Long Staple Egyptian Cotton</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_89876072-5da5-4e75-a490-cb11aeca06c3.jpg?v=1614587057"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            390.92
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">100% long staple cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. 300 thread count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability. This is the exact fabric I sold to 5-star luxury hotels of years. Higher thread count or heavier fabric does not mean better quality or comfort.  Textile experts: the construction is 173x120 using 60 compact yarns in both the warp and the weft - it doesn't get any better. Hypoallergenic will reduce allergens.  Sateen finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen. Double stitched seams for quality and durability. Perfectly covers your pillow with enough overhang to not see the pillow or you can tuck back into the pillow for a cleaner look.  Easy care - wash in warm water, dry on medium heat, and take out of the dryer as soon as they are done, or just before they are fully dry. If you are at all unsatisfied, simply let us know and you will receive a full refund - no questions asked! Includes: 10 - Dozen pillowcases with 4” hem</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549150957720</id>
      <title>Default Title / Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">390.92</s:price>
      <s:sku>T300 pillowcase standard - 20 - Case</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549149122712</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:23:08-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:23:08-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/wholesale-box-of-120-pillowcases-100-cotton-high-thread-count-luxury-pillow-cases-z-style-hem-stitch-standard-21x30-fits-20x26-pillow-sage"/>
    <title>Wholesale box of 120 Pillowcases. 100% Cotton, High Thread Count, Luxury Pillow Cases, Z-Style Hem Stitch, Standard 21x30 (fits 20x26 Pillow) - Sage</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_bfddac7b-151d-48fe-a5aa-2a2414ae7dfa.jpg?v=1614586990"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            484.50
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Our pillowcases have been the top selling products in the category on Amazon for over 4 years! 100% long staple cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability.  Hypoallergenic will reduce allergens. Sateen finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen.Double stitched seams for quality and durability.Easy care - wash in warm water, dry on medium heat, and take out of the dryer as soon as they are done, or just before they are fully dry. 100% Money Back Guarantee! If you are at all unsatisfied, simply let us know and you will receive a full refund - no questions asked!  Includes: Two pillowcases with "Z" stitched hem</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549149122712</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">484.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>VTC - ZH Pillowcase 2 - S - Sage - Case</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549148991640</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:23:04-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:23:04-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/wholesale-box-of-60-pillowcases-lilac-100-cotton-high-thread-count-pillow-cases-single-needle-hem-stitch-king-21x40-fits-20x36-pillow"/>
    <title>Wholesale box of 60 Pillowcases (Lilac). 100% Cotton, High Thread Count Pillow Cases, Single Needle Hem Stitch, King 21x40 (fits 20x36 Pillow)</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_7cecd90f-cc02-4d44-afe2-8b38dbe39638.jpg?v=1614586985"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            242.25
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">Our products have been the top selling products in the category on Amazon for over 4 years! 100% long staple cotton is breathable to keep you cool in the summer and dry and warm in the winter. High thread count is perfect for maximum comfort and durability.  Hypoallergenic will reduce allergens. Sateen finish for a smooth surface and luminous sheen.Double stitched seams for quality and durability.Easy care - wash in warm water, dry on medium heat, and take out of the dryer as soon as they are done, or just before they are fully dry. 100% Money Back Guarantee! If you are at all unsatisfied, simply let us know and you will receive a full refund - no questions asked!  Includes: Two pillowcases with single needle hem</td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549148991640</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">242.25</s:price>
      <s:sku>VTC - SN Pillowcase 2 - K - Lilac - Case</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549148434584</id>
    <published>2021-03-01T03:22:33-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-01T03:22:33-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://americanpillowcase.com/products/wholesale-box-of-144-polycotton-standard-size-pillowcases-white-200-thread-count-21x30-white-fits-20-x26-pillow-perfect-for-physical-therapy-clinics-hotels-camps"/>
    <title>Wholesale Box of 144 Polycotton Standard Size Pillowcases, White 200 Thread Count, 21&quot;x30&quot; White (Fits 20&quot; X26&quot; Pillow), Perfect for Physical Therapy Clinics, Hotels, Camps</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>American Pillowcase</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0013/8775/7686/products/medium_11edb997-7010-4090-bf87-0c9d03ef094a.jpg?v=1623909012"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>American Pillowcase<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            356.40
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2">American Pillowcase has been selling hotel quality pillowcases for 15 years. These pillowcases are great for hotels, Airbnb, camps, crafts, physical therapy clinics, embroidery. Please check your pillow size to make sure you order the correct size.<br><br>These are 200 thread count, hotel-quality pillowcases made of 60% cotton and 40% polyester for cotton-rich comfort. Ring-spun yarn construction provides strength, smoothness, and softness.<br><br>These are great if you want less wrinkling than cotton. If you want to print on them or tie dye them, 100% cotton works better, but these work as well. We also sell 100% cotton pillowcases and brushed microfiber pillowcases in other listings.<br><ul>
<li>HOTEL QUALITY – 200 thread count, bright white, 2” hem, strong percale weave.</li>
<li>WRINKLE RESISTANCE &amp; EASY CARE – 60% cotton 40% polyester makes long-lasting with no ironing needed yet still comfortable. Machine wash and dry</li>
<li>OTHER OPTIONS – We also sell wholesale, bulk packed 100% cotton and brushed microfiber pillowcases in other listings</li>
<li>STANDARD SIZE – 21”x30“ (fits 20”x26” pillow) - 2 Dozen</li>
<li>Great for hotels, Airbnb, camps, crafts, physical therapy clinics, and embroidery</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Pillowcases Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://americanpillowcase.com/products/6549148434584</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">356.40</s:price>
      <s:sku>Box_of_144_std_polycotton_pillowcases</s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
